RANDY PANOPIO

www.randypanopio.ca randypanopio@gmail.com (778) - 926 - 8693 Vancouver, B.C

A design oriented developer with a core focus on user experience. Coming from a diverse background with interests from film writing, cinematography, to history research and digital art, I try to bridge ideas and create touchpoints in all of the projects that I partake in.

Skills

Design & Technical

Test Driven Development, Agile Experience, UX / UI Design, Conducting Playtests, Gameplay Design, Creative Writing, Iterative Design Process, User Research Methodology

Toolkit

Unity, 3D Modelling (Maya), Character Rigging, IK Animations, Shaders (Shader Graphs), Pixel Art & Animations, Vector Illustrations, Adobe Suite (PS, AE, PR, XD, AI), Agile (Jira, Trello, Kanban)

Development

Proficient: C#, JS, Web Stack Competent: Java, PHP, Python Git, GitHub, Sourcetree, Web Frameworks

Education

Simon Fraser University

Interactive Arts and Technology (SIAT), Bachelor of Science -Concentration of Interactive Systems

2015 - 2020

Work Experience

Under the GUI Academy Inc.

Programming Instructor - Contractor

Richmond, B.C **Dec 2020 - June 2021**

Taught children ages 7 - 16 concepts of programming through hands on Unity and website projects during weekly online class sessions.

- Introduced concepts regarding programming foundations, web development, and game design to children with various levels of skill
- Volunteered creating personalized coding challenges for advanced students who showed interest in expanding their programming repertoire

Safe Software Inc. Front-End Web Developer - Co-op

Surrey, B.C **May 2018 - Dec 2018**

Acted as a front-end developer and the primary interface designer, maintaining and building web interfaces for a suite of enterprise GIS management tools.

- Collaborated with a team of developers, product managers, and stakeholders working on a new core feature (Automations), on an enterprise web application used by over 10,000 organizations across the world
- Designed and implemented three new UI for new features built upon existing management tools with over 100 individual UI elements, within 3 design iterations and testing phase completed in the span of 4 months
- Worked in an agile and test-driven development environment, building from a hybrid web frameworks while maintaining and authoring unit tests during production

Projects

Kagai **Dungeon Crawler - Unity**

Solo Project **Aug 2020 - Present**

A passion indie game project, touching on procedural generation algorithms, designing functional Ul's, architecting and programming game systems and mechanics, and authoring shaders.

- Constructed internal design tools allowing effortless and rapid prototyping
- Refined and programmed game systems by applying research methodology and feedback integration from continuous playtesting sessions

Frigid - Glacial Path to the South Narrative Visual Novel - Web

School Project Feb 2019 - Apr 2019

A narrative driven, collaborative project built for the web, focused on guiding players through an atmospheric world and immersive story.

- Integrated and extended a visual novel library through JS, and implementing the resource systems and scripted gameplay scenarios
- Worked as the creative writer and visual director of the project, adding 15 unique locations, 12 story branches, and over 100 lines of dialogue